<resources>
    <string name="app_name">About Me</string>
    <string name="text_name">Leonardo Rosa</string>
    <string name="yellow_star">Yellow star</string>
    <string name="bio">Unicode is an international not-for-profit organisation that started in the 1980s as an effort to "unify" the "codes" for textual characters used in the computing industry. By "code", I just mean a number. Computers only understand numbers, and so you need to tell the computer which number refers to the letter "a", which one refers to the letter "b", etc. so that you can visualise them on a computer
        screen (otherwise youd be reading ones and zeros right now). So the problem in the 1980s was that there wasnt a universally agreed-upon set of rules for which number refers to which character, and so every programmer was writing their own set of rules, and whenever their programs interacted with programs written by other programmers, theyd need to make specially designed translators to allow the programs to communicate. Unicode sought to solve this by creating an international standard - meaning that everyone would be using the same number-to-letter rule book.
Okay, so how does this relate to generating small text? Well, as it turned out, there were a bunch of people that werent too interested in Unicode. They had specific character requirements that Unicode hadnt accounted for in their initial specification. So in order to get programmers and organisations to adopt the Unicode standard faster, Unicode began incorperating a bunch of weird symbols and rules that those people needed for their applications, and thus Unicodes full character set exploded to include include tens of thousands of different symbols, for many languages, and many arcane legacy systems.
Along the way, it picked up a set of symbols which can be used to emulate "small caps" (an alphabet of small capital letters), and a somewhat incomplete set of subscript and superscript characters. So the small text letters that you see in the output box above are just a few of the 130,000+ symbols that are specified in the Unicode standard - just like the symbols that youre reading right now.
So while you might have thought that you were looking for small text fonts, it turns out that youre actually looking for small text symbols (or characters). People just assume it must be a font because they look different to normal characters - but so do emojis! And theyre not a font - theyre also characters in the Unicode standard. And thats pretty cool, because it means you can copy and paste the small text that this site generates into your Instagram bio, Twitter posts, Discord messages, Tumblr blog posts, YouTube comments, and just about anywhere else!</string>
    <string name="whats_your_nickname">What is your nickname?</string>
    <string name="done_button">DONE</string>
</resources>
